Hey, Jae-gul, did you find it?
I didn't hear you.
A little more
Go deep and look for it
I definitely saw it
Okay
Is anyone there?
GHOST TRAIN
Hello
I'm Kim Da-kyung
I contacted you before
Thank you, Sir.
This is hot
Did you say YouTuber?
YouTuber creator
This is why...
Here you go
Horror Queen
I'm warning you
If your heart is weak
Right now, this place
You'd better get out
Horror Queen
Transform
You don't know, do you?
You asked to see me,
What's the reason?
That...
I heard a rumor
At Gwanglim Station
Rumer's of strange things take place here.
Is it true?
sorry but...
Get out,
There's not been people like you
here in quite a will.
they take advantage of other people's
pain for money
To people like that
I have anything to say
If it's about money
Didn't you say you needed money?
Get out of here
I prepared a present just in case
How many times do I have to tell you
Isn't that Andong?
from the Joseon Dynasty
Made in Jeolla and Hwanghae Province
the best in country.
Sir, tell me what should I do
with this precious thing?
In Jeonju, my grandfather
runs a brewing business
Are you going to tell me?
Bu... But still
It's hard
All right, then.
wait...
How about just one?
This story
starts with a young man
Attention passengers
due to a problem on this line,
we have come to a full stop.
Excuse me.
sorry for the inconvenience
Until the incident is resolved,
Please wait patiently.
Our train will be leaving soon
Redon French Black.
Mister.
Don't touch it, if you aren't going buy it.
Not this one
French black, please
Where's French Black
Excuse me.
Not that one
that one there
Yes, that one
You really couldn't find it
What university do you go to?
What?
this is French black
That's French Yogo
It's the same brand
it's common sense
is its The one in the same row
That's what you should look for
but You keep looking in the wrong place
- It's 9,500 won
- Yes
You didn't give me the right one?
Oh, I didn't give you
Idiot, what the fuck you talking about?
There's no damn bag
why she's like that
stupid
This stop is
Yongdam
It's Yongdam Station
The door you're going to get off is
To the right
stupid
Ahh, shi...
fuck me.
Hello?
Uh, why?
My dear son, did you eat?
Did you drink again?
Mom, I'm going to hang up
because I'm watching a lecture
there you go again.
It's been a while since you came out the academy
I heard it's been more than two months
- I'm hanging up
- I'm worried about you
Mom.
Mom?
What is this?
[Women in her 20's commits
suicide by jumping of...]
This Station
Gwanglim
Gwanglim Station next stop
The door will open on the right
[The Shinseok-dong train has
left the station]
[Next train is an express]
Since then the case has been
ruled a suicide
You liking it?
That's enough of storys
You're gonna have to go
Perhaps, next time?
Don't ever come back
[Another man in his 20's commits suicide
at Gwanglim Station, in 16th suicide]
- Da-kyung?
- What?
- Why so surprised?
- No, it's not
You taken off your glasses
Your eyes
are pretty
Oh, so how did it go?
I like it a lot.
I knew it.
I knew you get it done,
and get the item.
Oh, item
Item
A few years ago
at Gwanglim Station
There was a suicide case
Suicide by jumping?
What's this?
It's too dull.
I like the feeling of this one.
Oh, really?
But
I don't think the view count
it will go up
Da-Kyung, the last story,
it too was dull
It didn't have much subs.
it was removed
Beauty YouTube and horror YouTube
We are different
even if it's dull
There are a lot of people that like it
So
Last video only
have about...
100 people watching it?
Rina, Aren't you going film?
Oh, right.
what do you even know.
She don't know shit.
The one you talked about last time
It's good, but..
Is there anything darker?
You know, your YouTube channel
I saw that,
There are less than 100 views
Previously
It was 100,000
oh my, and
so Suddenly?
It's just
Suddenly, its all beauty YouTubers
its like a new flavor
new flavor
And
lately Horror content,
Has been dropping.
if that all you have to do,
Why do this at all?
Because
I...
I'm
Horror Queen
Da-kyung
This
Should I change this?
There was a student
What you don't have
in order to have
It's a pain of pain
I used to endure it
I'd like to inform the passengers
on this train
due to the problem of the next station
We have come to a sudden stop
I'm sorry for the inconvenience
until the problem is settled
Please wait patiently
Our train is leaving soon
There must have been an accident
Did someone jump off again?
Oh, Mi-Joo
Professor
Hey, it's been a long time
Have you been well?
This stop is
Shindam
this is Shindam Station
What about study's?
Are you working hard?
Mi-Joo is kind of
I think I've become more feminine?
Did you lose weight?
And Professor also
You've gotten cooler
oh, really?
Professor, perhaps
Did you move?
The cafe that you taught me in
I've been there a few times...
oppa
Jin-ah
Why are you standing there?
You're not sitting down?
Who this?
She looks so cute?
Ah.
This is a past
student who I was tutoring
tutoring?
Say hello
She's is girlfriend
Professor
I'll get off here
Oh, ok
It was nice to meet you
She's got double eyelids, right?
What's wrong with you
What should we eat?
What to eat?
What do you want to eat?
You're nose
It's so pretty
Thank you.
That nose
It's so pretty
[Lee Jin it's you're turn]
Right now, all lines are busy
wait for representative,
I'll put you through.
Yes, it's 112 emergency
I'm in a station right now
Someone crazy person is after me.
They're chasing after me with acid?
They are holding acid,
and saying they're coming for you?
I hid in the bathroom
Please tell me the exact location
Gwanglim...
Gwanglim Station
Is this the women's restroom at Gwanglim Station?
Yes, hurry up
Please hurry up and come.
Calm down
What did the woman look like
Let me know.
She has bandages on her face
wearing a hospital outfit
Hello?
How did you know it was a woman?
That nose
It's so pretty
You're nose
You're so pretty
You don't believe me.
Uh, no
It's not that
but that story
Where did you hear it?
Oh, my
I must be drunk
the subway
the number of people per day
7.3 million people
Average daily time usage
35.1 minutes
And
record the highest number of missing persons in the country
the Mysterious Gwanglim Station
All right.
Right now, I'm
at Gwanglim Station
Did you see it?
I think it's a poltergeist
Poltergeist, right
Poltergeist is right
- Say something
- Now?
All right.
I
The True mysterious story of
Gwanglim Station
I'm going to play it for you
I'm warning you
If you have a weak heart
Right now, this place
You'd better get out
Horror Queen
Da-kyung
How is it?
Ms. Da-kyung
All right.
Horror Queen is back
The story is fun, also
The development is fast
It's not bad?
Thank you...
Thank you.
What?
What do we got here?
Did you just see it?
What?
What...
What is that?
It's not?
This is a ghost, right?
This never happened in the past,
Its's never been filmed?
Do you want a drink
Oh, I...
I've stopped drinking
You said you had a lot of views
Let's celebrate
Well, one more drink
What do you think the subway is?
Public transportation... Right?
Well in general, yes?
But to someone It's life also
In the beginning it wasn't bad
Like any office worker
It was normal
But little by little
I'm starting to lose what I had
well-earned but
My job is gone
And then family
Next, moderation
as such
falling and falling
until you have
nowhere to fall
but To the cold floor
Mister
Get up
Hurry up and get up
You can't sleep here
Oh My.
You see
People are passing by
Please move that way
Oh, Mister
Don't touch it if you are buying it
It's always Mr. Lee.
here.
Oh, this is not it
I'm asking for redon French black.
What do we got here?
Did you move to this place?
Why are you scared?
Oh, what's in your pocket
Take it out
Eon-nung, Lee, shi, T
Is this it?
Let's say hi more often
affectionately
that fucking bastard
That's right
I'm gonna kill you, son of a bitch
Hey, you son of bitch
Do I look like shit
You motherfucker
Fucker
Fuck that fucking asshole.
fuck
ahh, shi...
Mr. Kim?
Mr. Kim is that you?
what's with that outfit? Huh?
It's very, very, very...
What are you doing
If there's anything good,
We have to share with each other.
How can you be so mean,
When I look like this
Oh, this is
What's wrong with me?
You, shi...
No, no, no
Help me, please.
Excuse me
It's 4,400 won
Sir, you're change
ah, fuck
No, don't
Ah, shi...
Help me!
Since then
there are clothes that don't have owners
that are often found in the station
So...
if you liked it
Is that what you wanted?
Yeah, I'm going to use it all
Those who ignore me
I won't let you go
Congratulations
For what?
Viewership exceeded 300,000
Thank you.
by the way
I was just going to congratulate you,
I also wanted to see you
To be honest
I like you, Da-Kyung
All this
For Rina
I think all will look good on you
- Really?
- Yes
Please pick one
Everything looks good
Really?
No, honestly, how can you be so shameless
as a beauty YouTuber
when you don't even do your own makeup?
No matter how fun it is
you should have at least a
modicum of conscience, right?
someone like that,
acting like that all the time?
What's the difference between
those who are "star-struck"
a sick person
That was what I was talking about
They say that when you hate someone for no reason
it's because you see yourself in them.
Who says such nonsense?
Or you could just say no.
Is it really worth yelling about?
I'm sorry.
I'm so angry
What do you hate about her so much?
Her popularity is based on lies.
really?
Is it because of that?
I think this would be better?
This seems good
Thank you.
I don’t know that either.
People are always
desiring what they don't have.
If you look at what you have
I'm sure you be happy
If you try to covet what you don't have,
you could lose everything
I'd have to agree with you.
Even if I live
There's not much time left
So
You too
Why don't you stop coming
What's this?
1 million hearts
Congratulations, Da-kyung
A million, a million, a million, a million
A million, a million, a million
A million, a million
Congratulations on reaching 1 million hearts
Mr. Da-kyung
Thank you.
Thank you
[@heee 1day ago]
[This is all true! You should never go there. I've been before.]
Enjoy your meal.
Ms. Da-kyung
This?
All right.
Your videos
You have to take them all down
Why?
Because The world must never
know about it
What do you mean?
At the convenience store in Gwanglim Station
I had a strange experience
What
Gwanglim Bridge
Gwanglim Bridge?
A cult disappeared there decades ago
That's right
Gwanglim Station
was built on the site of the Gwanglim Church's chapel.
That's why strange things
keep happening.
Wait a minute
What do you mean?
Da-kyung
You can't go there.
If you go there, you'll all die.
What are you doing? Let go of this hand.
Video production
I have to take it down.
[The Mysterious cult of Gwanglim Bridge]
[Gwanglim Chruch mass suicide]
[50 years ago today church mass suicide]
[Oct.3,1973 40 church members
committed suicide in Gwang Chapel]
Your videos
You have to take them all down.
[Horror Queen Da-Kyung]
Why?
The world must never
know about it.
[Delete Channel]
If you do this,
you will achieved your goal.
If you keep going,
You can easily get what you want.
So Now
How about we just stop?
Oh, wait a minute.
That got a lot of views.
Fighting!
Da-kyung
I'll go first.
I'll talk to you later.
What's wrong?
You haven't even greeted me since morning.
Do you have anything to say?
I
If you have time tonight,
would you like to go out for dinner?
The takoyaki place I mentioned last time
should still be open.
Actually,
I wanted us to go together last night
But I was out of town
You were at the office
yesterday evening?
Huh?
Yesterday, PD Kim and I
were out all day.
Bad Time?
It Wouldn't be possible?
No
I have time.
But with a person like you
I think it's better to keep it professional.
We need to talk more.
Yes
If possible,
I'm absolutely certain.
I'm sorry,
I have nothing more to tell you.
Nothing?
I'm feeling much worse.
Even at the hospital,
They told me to stop working.
Then just one.
Just one last thing.
Huh?
A whopping one million people
Isn't that enough?
More
I need more likes.
You already
got what you wanted.
What more do you
need?
Fuck
That's why I came here.
Let's just end it here.
What is that?
You don't have much time left anyway.
Just like you.
There was someone similar.
Like you
A person who lives for the attention of others
I didn't know
How different, though.
But guys
You know I don't really introduce just anything, right?
This
Is also a great editing tip
that won't break down until you leave work.
I tried it and really liked it.
Is it purely about sharing?
Of course, it's an advertisement.
This stop is Gangnam Terminal.
This is Gangnam Terminal Station.
Babies
I have arrived.
That's it for today.
Bye
What?
Ah, this is annoying.
As expected.
I knew you could do it.
Suicide by jumping?
Ugh, what is this?
It's too dull?
I like the feeling of this one.
Ah~
Really?
Don't be so mean to Da-kyung.
Huh?
Why's at?
what are you talking about?
That way, we can stimulate each other and have a good time.
You know that only Da-kyung gets stimulated, right?
Woo-jin PD
You know that's really strange.
As if I care about her?
So, when can I help you with the filming?
No help,
let's just go eat together.
Rina
Rina?
Nosebleed
Ha, This is so embarrassing.
Have you recently touched something
dirty with your hands or something?
Have you ever done that?
No?
Never before
Ah, shit
I remembered.
Did I touch something weird on the subway?
Like mucus.
mucus?
Oh, Doctor.
This isn't some kind of bacterial infection, is it?
First, I'll prescribe
you some medicine.
and
let's see how things go, okay?
Oh, no, it's dirty.
And, this here.
Could you please sign this?
Ouch. Of course.
Doctor,
how did you find out?
Huh?
I'm somewhat famous, you know.
I'm the industry's No. 1 beauty YouTuber.
That's not it...
Please sign this consent form.
Sign the consent here
Oh, this is embarrassing.
Huh? Da-kyung
What you doing here?
The story...
Oh, right.
That dull story?
But
Da-kyung, surely you not
lying about the story
You're not here to spy on me, are you?
What?
Oh, just kidding.
Well, I hope it goes well.
That way, Da-kyung
will be able to sign a good contract.
Yes.
Is there anything else you'd like to say?
No
Not really
blood
Rina
It's starting now.
Million, million, million
A million, a million, a million
Thank you
Thank you~
That's awesome!
Applause!
A million Let's go~
Let's go~
I'm Rina
#1 Beauty YouTuber
I'm Rina from Rina World
This station is...
Gwanglim, This is Gwanglim Station.
The exit door is on the right.
Excuse me.
By any chance,
Are you Rina?
Can I help you?
It's okay, it's okay.
Are you sure you're okay?
Oh, please get out!
It's Gwanglim Bridge.
Have you heard of it?
I heard everything.
This subway station
was originally the Gwanglim Church's chapel.
Because of that,
strange things keep happening here.
There's even a record of them committing suicide together
to ensure the leader's immortality.
Also
Some people believe
the cult leader is alive Somewhere right now.
Is that really possible?
What if such a thing really exists?
I want to report on it.
That group called Gwanglimgyo.
Would you like to meet them in person?
didn't answer the phone.
After the beep,
please leave a voicemail.
It's time.
I'd rather not eat with someone like you.
I think it's better to keep it professional.
Woo-jin
Are you looking for Da-kyung?
Who are you?
Hi, I'm from Mapo Police Station,
I'm Detective Park Joo-oh
Do you know where she is?
Oh, if you don't mind,
what's going on?
I just watched her YouTube video.
Friday
3:34 PM
There be a train coming in.
If you get on that train
You'll be able to meet him.
The train for...is now arriving.
The train for...is approaching.
Passengers,
After everyone has disembarked
Please board safely.
[PD Woo-Jin]
The train is now arriving.
The platform safety door will open.
Our train
will depart shortly.
The station chief
is Someone else?
but in the video, she clearly says
that she interviewed the station chief.
Well, the recording
was also uploaded.
But the person in charge there
is a different person.
Then
The person Da-kyung interviewed is
three years ago
He's went missing.
Hello?
I knew it the moment I saw you.
You're desire would lead you here.
You were always curious about the story,
But you never really wondered about me.
Who am I?
And why am I telling you this?
The last story I'll tell you is
It's my story.
What are you looking at?
Hey, over there
I thought I saw someone there just now?
Is it this time?
There's definitely someone there
Someone got in there.
Oh, no, I don't want to.
I have to go to that office. Sir.
Sir, shi...
Stop feeding the cat.
is it a pig or a cat, you idiot?
It's Ming ming.
A pig?
Stop talking nonsense.
You're already here.
If someone gets in,
what are you going to do?
Huh?
Hey, last time you were talking
this and that about that cult
you're going to film that YouTube video
Because of all that
You know how embarrassed I was
I was there too
So...
You're going this time too.
Oh, it's always just me...
Is there anyone on the subway at this hour?
Oh, o h my...
Excuse me.
Is anyone there?
No.
Hey, Jae-gul did you find anyone?
No one is there.
Hey, go deeper and look.
I clearly saw it.
Yes.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey Jae-gul
Come back the way you came
Hello
Hey, Jae-gul
More...
It's hot
Hello
Hey, Jae-gul
Oh, why is it so hot in here?
Hey, Jae-gul!
Is that you Jae-gul?
What is this?
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, hot.
Ah, shit.
Station chef
Hello.
Is this Jae-gul?
I
It's the station.
Hey, call me.
I'm here.
I'm stuck on the subway.
Where are you now?
20...
I see...
Hey, Jae-gul,
Where are you now?
I'm going...
I can see it.
I'll be there soon...
Station chef
Can see me?
Open the door
You've probably heard that
This place originally was
the Gwanglim Church worship hall.
I can help you meet him.
Please open the door.
The times I spent with you
were quite enjoyable.
However you
I'm going to miss.
Open the door...
Open it!
Open!
Mister
The train to Singeol-dong
has just left.
Da-kyung
Ah, Da-kyung
Why aren't you answering my phone?
I was worried...
Woo-jin
Shall I tell you an interesting story?